Devesh Mhatre

https://github.com/deveshmhatre • https://devesh-mhatre.netlify.app • deveshmhtr.mhatre92@gmail.com • 9028250240

Professional Summary

I am a senior front-end developer with three years of meaningful contributions, both as a sole product owner and as part of teams of varying size and scope. In order to continuously learn and grow as a developer, I have developed a tendency to accept feedback from senior and junior developers alike. I have experience driving projects forward as the front-end development team lead, regardless of whether it's a legacy project or a new concept. I aim to tackle more complex problems and continue to find ways of improving user experience.

Education

Tilak Maharashtra Vidyapeeth

Bachelor of Business Administration, Marketing

Navi Mumbai, MH 2016-2019

Experience

F22 Labs Global Remote

Senior Front-end Developer

April, 2021 – January, 2024

- Develop and maintain front-end properties across multiple frameworks, including ReactJS, NextJS, AngularJS,
- Develop, distribute and maintain React Native apps on Google Play Store and Apple App Store
- Lead React Native upgrade activities for compatibility with new Android and iOS versions
- Collaborate with managers, designers and QA engineers for requirement gathering before beginning development
- Collaborate with backend developers to integrate RESTful APIs with both web-based and app-based front-ends

Wavel Al Remote

Digital Marketing Intern

January, 2021 - April, 2021

Ghatkopar, MH

- Manage social media accounts using Hootsuite
- Manage company blog using WordPress
- Design and write content for social media marketing

Cuemath **Business Development Intern** October, 2018 – January, 2019

• Corresponded with prospective customers and partners

- Conducted live seminars and product demos
- Helped automate daily report generation process

Skills & Interests

Technical: ReactJS, React Native, NextJS, AngularJS, Rails, Javascript, Typescript, Ruby, Python, Git, Redux, Xcode

Language: English, Marathi, Hindi

Interests: Reading, writing, programming